<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D&amp;D Adventures</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on D&amp;D Adventures</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Blood</title>
      <link>/post/first-blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/first-blood/</guid>
      <description>Over five hundred years ago, a pact was made between a clan of gnomes and dwarves which became known as the Phandelver Pact. Together they mined the magically rich ores within Wave Echo Cave. Human spellcasters from nearby Phandalin joined forces with them and together they combined their collective skills to create a forge to craft magical items dubbed the Forge of Spells. Everything came to an abrupt end when orcs, craving magical treasures, besieged Phandalin and the Wave Echo Cave mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Adulting with Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons My name is Jav and gaming has always been a part of my life. I convinced a few friends to learn D&amp;amp;D together so I volunteered to be the Dungeon Master (&amp;ldquo;DM&amp;rdquo;) for D&amp;amp;D Starter Set campaign, The Lost Mine of Phandelver.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always enjoyed storytelling, fantasy, gaming, envisioning crazy worlds, and spending time with friends. As I write this, COVID-19 is forcing us to practice social distancing and roleplaying with friends (over teleconferencing tools - we&amp;rsquo;re using Skype) has been a much needed escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resources/</guid>
      <description>The core of D&amp;amp;D is storytelling. You and your friends tell a story together, guiding your heroes through quests for treasure, battles with deadly foes, daring rescues, courtly intrigue, and much more. You can also explore the world of Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons through any of the novels written by its fantasy authors, as well as engaging board games and immersive video games. All of these stories are part of D&amp;amp;D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map</title>
      <link>/map/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/map/</guid>
      <description>Where are we now? A cave mouth entered at in the dead of night. Light from the Full moon bounces off the small stream, illuminating the entry way&amp;hellip; The cleric&amp;rsquo;s darkvision was taken for granted for too long&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>